{
    "studyset": "22676264",
    "data": [
        {
            "question": "water",
            "answer": "shuǐ"
        },
        {
            "question": "away",
            "answer": "lí"
        },
        {
            "question": "good",
            "answer": "hǎo"
        },
        {
            "question": "want",
            "answer": "yào"
        },
        {
            "question": "over",
            "answer": "guò"
        },
        {
            "question": "how",
            "answer": "zěn me"
        },
        {
            "question": "did",
            "answer": "zuò"
        },
        {
            "question": "man",
            "answer": "nán rén"
        },
        {
            "question": "going",
            "answer": "qù"
        },
        {
            "question": "where",
            "answer": "nǎ lǐ"
        },
        {
            "question": "would",
            "answer": "huì"
        },
        {
            "question": "or",
            "answer": "huò zhě"
        },
        {
            "question": "took",
            "answer": "ná"
        },
        {
            "question": "school",
            "answer": "xué xiào"
        },
        {
            "question": "think",
            "answer": "xiǎng"
        },
        {
            "question": "home",
            "answer": "jiā"
        },
        {
            "question": "who",
            "answer": "shuí"
        },
        {
            "question": "didn’t",
            "answer": "méi yǒu"
        },
        {
            "question": "ran",
            "answer": "pǎo"
        },
        {
            "question": "know",
            "answer": "zhī dào"
        },
        {
            "question": "bear",
            "answer": "xióng"
        },
        {
            "question": "can’t",
            "answer": "bù néng"
        },
        {
            "question": "again",
            "answer": "zài"
        },
        {
            "question": "cat",
            "answer": "māo"
        },
        {
            "question": "long",
            "answer": "cháng"
        },
        {
            "question": "things",
            "answer": "shì qing"
        },
        {
            "question": "new",
            "answer": "xīn"
        },
        {
            "question": "after",
            "answer": "yǐ hòu"
        },
        {
            "question": "wanted",
            "answer": "yào"
        },
        {
            "question": "eat",
            "answer": "chī"
        },
        {
            "question": "everyone",
            "answer": "měi gè rén"
        },
        {
            "question": "our",
            "answer": "wǒ men de"
        },
        {
            "question": "two",
            "answer": "liǎng"
        },
        {
            "question": "has",
            "answer": "yǒu"
        },
        {
            "question": "yes",  
            "answer": "shì de"
        },
        {
            "question": "play",
            "answer": "wán"
        },
        {
            "question": "take",
            "answer": "ná"
        },
        {
            "question": "thought",
            "answer": "xiǎng"
        },
        {
            "question": "dog",
            "answer": "gǒu"
        },
        {
            "question": "well",
            "answer": "hǎo"
        },
        {
            "question": "find",
            "answer": "zhǎo dào"
        },
        {
            "question": "more",
            "answer": "gèng"
        },
        {
            "question": "I’ll",
            "answer": "wǒ huì"
        },
        {
            "question": "round",
            "answer": "yīng"
        },
        {
            "question": "tree",
            "answer": "shù"
        },
        {
            "question": "magic",
            "answer": "mó fǎ"
        },
        {
            "question": "shouted",
            "answer": "hū hū"
        },
        {
            "question": "us",
            "answer": "wǒ men"
        },
        {
            "question": "other",
            "answer": "lìng wài"
        },
        {
            "question": "food",
            "answer": "shí wù"
        },
        {
            "question": "fox",
            "answer": "hú li"
        },
        {
            "question": "through",
            "answer": "tōng guò"
        },
        {
            "question": "way",
            "answer": "fāng shì"
        },
        {
            "question": "been",
            "answer": "cún zài"
        },
        {
            "question": "stop",
            "answer": "zhǐ"
        },
        {
            "question": "must",
            "answer": "bì xū"
        },
        {
            "question": "red",
            "answer": "hóng"
        },
        {
            "question": "door",
            "answer": "mén"
        },
        {
            "question": "right",
            "answer": "duì"
        },
        {
            "question": "sea",
            "answer": "hǎi"
        },
        {
            "question": "these",
            "answer": "zhè xiē"
        },
        {
            "question": "began",
            "answer": "kāi shǐ"
        },
        {
            "question": "boy",
            "answer": "nán hái"
        },
        {
            "question": "animals",
            "answer": "dòng wù"
        },
        {
            "question": "never",
            "answer": "yǒng yuǎn bù"
        },
        {
            "question": "next",
            "answer": "xià yī ge"
        },
        {
            "question": "first",
            "answer": "dì yī"
        },
        {
            "question": "work",
            "answer": "gōng zuò"
        },
        {
            "question": "lots",
            "answer": "hěn duō"
        },
        {
            "question": "need",
            "answer": "xū yào"
        },
        {
            "question": "that’s",
            "answer": "zhè shì"
        },
        {
            "question": "baby",
            "answer": "bǎo bèi"
        },
        {
            "question": "fish",
            "answer": "yú"
        },
        {
            "question": "gave",
            "answer": "gěi"
        },
        {
            "question": "mouse",
            "answer": "láng"
        },
        {
            "question": "something",
            "answer": "shén me"
        },
        {
            "question": "bed",
            "answer": "chuáng"
        },
        {
            "question": "may",
            "answer": "kě néng"
        },
        {
            "question": "still",
            "answer": "hái"
        },
        {
            "question": "found",
            "answer": "fā xiàn"
        },
        {
            "question": "live",
            "answer": "huó zhe"
        },
        {
            "question": "say",
            "answer": "shuō"
        },
        {
            "question": "soon",
            "answer": "mǎ shàng"
        },
        {
            "question": "night",
            "answer": "wǎn shàng"
        },
        {
            "question": "narrator",
            "answer": "jiǎ shù"
        },
        {
            "question": "small",
            "answer": "xiǎo"
        },
        {
            "question": "car",
            "answer": "chē"
        },
        {
            "question": "couldn’t",
            "answer": "bù néng"
        },
        {
            "question": "three",
            "answer": "sān"
        },
        {
            "question": "head",
            "answer": "tóu"
        },
        {
            "question": "king",
            "answer": "wáng"
        },
        {
            "question": "town",
            "answer": "xiǎo chéng zhèn"
        },
        {
            "question": "I’ve",
            "answer": "wǒ yǒu"
        },
        {
            "question": "around",
            "answer": "zhōu wéi"
        },
        {
            "question": "every",
            "answer": "měi gè"
        },
        {
            "question": "garden",
            "answer": "huā yuán"
        },
        {
            "question": "fast",
            "answer": "kuài"
        },
        {
            "question": "only",
            "answer": "zhǐ yǒu"
        },
        {
            "question": "many",
            "answer": "hěn duō"
        },
        {
            "question": "laughed",
            "answer": "xiào"
        },
        {
            "question": "let’s",
            "answer": "ràng wǒ men"
        },
        {
            "question": "much",
            "answer": "hěn duō"
        },
        {
            "question": "suddenly",
            "answer": "tū rán"
        },
        {
            "question": "told",
            "answer": "gào su"
        },
        {
            "question": "another",
            "answer": "líng yī ge"
        },
        {
            "question": "great",
            "answer": "wěi dà"
        },
        {
            "question": "why",
            "answer": "wèi shén me"
        },
        {
            "question": "cried",
            "answer": "kū"
        },
        {
            "question": "keep",
            "answer": "bǎo chí"
        },
        {
            "question": "room",
            "answer": "fáng jiān"
        },
        {
            "question": "last",
            "answer": "zuì hòu"
        },
        {
            "question": "jumped",
            "answer": "tiào"
        },
        {
            "question": "because",
            "answer": "yīn wèi"
        },
        {
            "question": "even",
            "answer": "shěn zhì"
        },
        {
            "question": "am",
            "answer": "shì"
        },
        {
            "question": "before",
            "answer": "qián"
        },
        {
            "question": "gran",
            "answer": "nài nai"
        },
        {
            "question": "clothes",
            "answer": "yī fú"
        },
        {
            "question": "tell",
            "answer": "gào su"
        },
        {
            "question": "key",
            "answer": "yào shi"
        },
        {
            "question": "fun",
            "answer": "yóu xì"
        },
        {
            "question": "place",
            "answer": "dì fang"
        },
        {
            "question": "mother",
            "answer": "mǔ qīn"
        },
        {
            "question": "sat",
            "answer": "zuò zhe"
        },
        {
            "question": "boat",
            "answer": "chuán"
        },
        {
            "question": "window",
            "answer": "chuāng hù"
        },
        {
            "question": "sleep",
            "answer": "shuì jiào"
        },
        {
            "question": "feet",
            "answer": "jiǎo"
        },
        {
            "question": "morning",
            "answer": "zǎo shang"
        },
        {
            "question": "queen",
            "answer": "nǚ wáng"
        },
        {
            "question": "each",
            "answer": "měi ge"
        },
        {
            "question": "book",
            "answer": "shū"
        },
        {
            "question": "its",
            "answer": "tā de"
        },
        {
            "question": "green",
            "answer": "lǜ"
        },
        {
            "question": "different",
            "answer": "bù tóng"
        },
        {
            "question": "let",
            "answer": "ràng"
        },
        {
            "question": "girl",
            "answer": "nǚ hái"
        },
        {
            "question": "which",
            "answer": "nǎ yī ge"
        },
        {
            "question": "inside",
            "answer": "lǐ mian"
        },
        {
            "question": "run",
            "answer": "pǎo"
        },
        {
            "question": "any",
            "answer": "rén hé"
        },
        {
            "question": "under",
            "answer": "zài...xià"
        },
        {
            "question": "hat",
            "answer": "mào zi"
        },
        {
            "question": "snow",
            "answer": "xuě"
        },
        {
            "question": "air",
            "answer": "kōng qì"
        },
        {
            "question": "trees",
            "answer": "shù"
        },
        {
            "question": "bad",
            "answer": "huài"
        },
        {
            "question": "tea",
            "answer": "chá"
        },
        {
            "question": "top",
            "answer": "dǐng"
        },
        {
            "question": "eyes",
            "answer": "yǎn jīng"
        },
        {
            "question": "fell",
            "answer": "diào"
        },
        {
            "question": "friends",
            "answer": "péng yǒu"
        },
        {
            "question": "box",
            "answer": "hé zi"
        },
        {
            "question": "dark",
            "answer": "àn"
        },
        {
            "question": "grandad",
            "answer": "yé yé"
        },
        {
            "question": "there’s",
            "answer": "yǒu"
        },
        {
            "question": "looking",
            "answer": "kàn"
        },
        {
            "question": "end",
            "answer": "jié shù"
        },
        {
            "question": "than",
            "answer": "bǐ"
        },
        {
            "question": "best",
            "answer": "zuì hǎo"
        },
        {
            "question": "better",
            "answer": "gèng hǎo"
        },
        {
            "question": "hot",
            "answer": "rè"
        },
        {
            "question": "sun",
            "answer": "tài yáng"
        },
        {
            "question": "across",
            "answer": "duì miàn"
        },
        {
            "question": "gone",
            "answer": "zǒu le"
        },
        {
            "question": "hard",
            "answer": "nán"
        },
        {
            "question": "floppy",
            "answer": "ruǎn de"
        },
        {
            "question": "really",
            "answer": "zhēn de"
        },
        {
            "question": "wind",
            "answer": "fēng"
        },
        {
            "question": "wish",
            "answer": "yuàn"
        },
        {
            "question": "eggs",
            "answer": "jī dàn"
        },
        {
            "question": "once",
            "answer": "yī cì"
        },
        {
            "question": "please",
            "answer": "qǐng"
        },
        {
            "question": "thing",
            "answer": "shì qing"
        },
        {
            "question": "stopped",
            "answer": "zhǐ"
        },
        {
            "question": "ever",
            "answer": "yǒng yuǎn"
        },
        {
            "question": "miss",
            "answer": "xiǎng niàn"
        },
        {
            "question": "most",
            "answer": "zuì"
        },
        {
            "question": "cold",
            "answer": "lěng"
        },
        {
            "question": "park",
            "answer": "gōng yuán"
        },
        {
            "question": "lived",
            "answer": "zhù"
        },
        {
            "question": "birds",
            "answer": "niǎo"
        },
        {
            "question": "duck",
            "answer": "yā"
        },
        {
            "question": "horse",
            "answer": "mǎ"
        },
        {
            "question": "rabbit",
            "answer": "tù zi"
        },
        {
            "question": "white",
            "answer": "bái"
        },
        {
            "question": "coming",
            "answer": "lái"
        },
        {
            "question": "he’s",
            "answer": "tā shì"
        },
        {
            "question": "river",
            "answer": "hé"
        },
        {
            "question": "liked",
            "answer": "xǐ huān"
        },
        {
            "question": "giant",
            "answer": "jù rén"
        },
        {
            "question": "looks",
            "answer": "kàn qǐ lái"
        },
        {
            "question": "use",
            "answer": "shǐ yòng"
        },
        {
            "question": "along",
            "answer": "sòng"
        },
        {
            "question": "plants",
            "answer": "zhí wù"
        },
        {
            "question": "dragon",
            "answer": "lóng"
        },
        {
            "question": "pulled",
            "answer": "lā"
        },
        {
            "question": "we’re",
            "answer": "wǒ men"
        },
        {
            "question": "fly",
            "answer": "fēi"
        },
        {
            "question": "grow",
            "answer": "zhǎng dào"
        }
    ]
}